Can't bind to prop name because it isn't a known\h property of node. You may encounter this error\h\h
Can't bind to prop name because it isn't a known property of node.
when you attempt to bind to a property or\h attribute of an element, but that property\h\h
你可能在试图绑定某元素的 Property 或 Attribute，而
is unknown to Angular. It may be unknown for a\h variety of reasons. If it's an Angular component,\h\h
这可能出于多种原因。如果它是 Angular 组件
it might be missing the @Input decorator on the\h component definition. But if it's a native HTML\h\h
它可能在组件定义中忘了写 @Input 装饰器。但是如果它是原生 HTML 元素
element, it may be a property that just does\h not exist. Or, if you happen to be working with\h\h
它可能只是因为该属性不存在。或者，如果你在使用自定义元素或 Web Components
custom elements or web components, there may\h be additional configuration required to bind\h\h
它可能需要进行额外的配置，以绑定到自定义属性
to custom properties. Let's start with a quick\h review of how property binding works in Angular.\h\h
让我们先快速过一遍 Angular 属性绑定的工作原理
Then we'll examine several reproductions\h and resolutions for the issue. In an\h\h
然后，我们会检查一些错误重现并解决它们
Angular template we can bind to a property,\h by wrapping it in brackets, then provide an\h\h
在 Angular 模板中，我们可以通过把属性包裹在方括号中来绑定它
expression on the right side. When the value in\h the expression changes the bound property and\h\h
并且在其右侧提供表达式。当表达式的值发生变化时，被绑定的属性
UI will be updated automatically. In most cases\h you'll run into issues with unknown properties\h\h
及其对应的 UI 都会自动更新。 通常，你会在使用自定义组件时会遇到未知属性的问题
when working with your own custom components.\h In our code we have an ItemComponent with a name\h\h
在我们的代码中，我们有一个带有 name 属性的 ItemComponent
property. Then, in the AppComponent template we\h reference the App Item Component and attempt to\h\h
然后，在 AppComponent 模板中，我们引用了 ItemComponent
bind to the name property. But currently\h Angular tells us it can't bind to name,\h\h
并试图绑定到其 name 属性 但现在，Angular 告诉我们它无法绑定到 name
since it isn't a known property of 'app-item'.\h We can address the issue by going back into our\h\h
因为它不是一个 'app-item' 的已知属性 我们可以通过回到 ItemComponent，并且
ItemComponent and adding the input decorator to\h the name property. The @Input decorator allows\h\h
为 name 属性添加 @Input 装饰器来解决此问题
data to be bound or passed in from the outside of\h the component via the template. In other words,\h\h
这个 @Input 装饰器允许数据进行绑定或者说通过模板从组件的外部传入
if a property is not specified as an input it\h can't be used with brackets for data binding in\h\h
换句话说，如果某个属性没有被指定为 @Input，它就不能
the template. It's also worth noting that you\h can pass an argument to the @Input decorator\h\h
在模板中使用方括号进行数据绑定。 另请注意，你可以给 @Input 装饰器传入参数
to change the name of the property. That allows\h you to use a different name in the template\h\h
以改变该属性的名字。
than is used as the property name in the component\h itself. In addition to your custom components\h\h
这可以让你能在模板中使用与其组件内部属性名不同的名字
you might also run into this issue with native\h HTML elements. With the default configuration,\h\h
另外，你的自定义组件还可能出现与原生 HTML 元素相关的问题 在默认配置下
you can only bind to properties that the Angular\h compiler knows about. When working with native\h\h
你只能绑定 Angular 编译器认识的属性
HTML elements it knows about the properties\h and attributes from the HTML standard spec. For\h\h
当使用原生 HTML 元素时，它认识来自 HTML 规范的 Property 和 Attribute
example, here we have an input element and we're\h binding to the value attribute on that element.\h\h
比如，对于 Input 元素，我们可以绑定到该元素的 value 属性
At this point there's no error, because\h value is a valid attribute on an input,\h\h
这时不会发生错误，因为 value 是 input 的一个有效属性
but if we attempt to bind to an attribute that\h does not exist, then Angular will throw an error.\h\h
但如果我们试图绑定到一个不存在的属性，Angular 就会抛出错误
There's probably not a good reason to bind\h to a property that does not exist on a native\h\h
虽然并没有什么好的理由绑定到原生 HTML 元素中不存在的属性
HTML element. However it is possible to tell\h Angular to ignore this error within an ngModule.\h\h
但是仍然可以告诉 Angular 在某个 ngModule 中忽略这个错误
Angular core contains a NO_ERRORS_SCHEMA which we\h can add to the schema's array inside an ngModule\h\h
添加到 ngModule 装饰器中的 schemas 数组中
decorator. Notice how the error disappears when\h we update the schema. But keep in mind this is\h\h
注意，当我们修改这个 schema 的时候，错误消失了，但是要记住
generally a technique that you should only use\h as a last resort because it will bypass the error\h\h
这项技巧只应该作为不得已的手段使用，因为它会忽略所有此类错误
altogether which may lead to uncaught issues and\h unstable code in the future. Now one other area\h\h
而这会在未来给我们带来未捕获的问题和不稳定的代码
you may encounter this error is when working\h with web components or custom elements. When\h\h
另一个你可能遇到此问题的地方是使用 Web Components 或自定义元素时
working with a custom element it may be perfectly\h acceptable to bind to a property that Angular does\h\h
当使用自定义元素时，绑定到一个 Angular 不认识的属性是完全可以的
not know about. We can tell Angular to bypass the\h error in a more conservative way by applying the\h\h
我们可以用一种更保守的方式告诉 Angular 忽略本错误 那就是在 ngModule 中使用 CUSTOM_ELEMENTS_SCHEMA
CUSTOM_ELEMENTS_SCHEMA in the ngModule. This will\h tell Angular to bypass the known property error on\h\h
这会告诉 Angular 在自定义元素上忽略其已知属性的错误
custom elements like your own Angular\h components or third-party web components.\h\h
就像它们是你自己的 Angular 组件或第三方 Web 组件一样
That allows you to bind to any property on a\h custom element, but you'll still get errors\h\h
它会允许你在自定义元素上绑定任意属性，但是当
when attempting to bind to a non-existent\h property on a native HTML element. Let's go\h\h
在原生 HTML 元素上绑定到不存在的属性时仍然会报错
ahead and recap. When you encounter 'Can't bind\h to prop name since it isn't a known property of\h\h
我们来回顾一下。 当你遇到 'Can't bind to prop name since it isn't a known property of node'
node," you'll first want to verify that the\h prop name is known to Angular. While native\h\h
错误时，你首先要验证一下此属性名对 Angular 是已知的。
HTML elements should only use properties based\h on the actual HTML spec, when working with custom\h\h
原生 HTML 元素只应该使用基于现行 HTML 规范的属性
elements you can bypass the error by applying\h the CUSTOM_ELEMENTS_SCHEMA in an ngModule,\h\h
当使用自定义元素时，你可以通过在 ngModule 中 使用 CUSTOM_ELEMENTS_SCHEMA 来忽略本错误
or as a last resort you can bypass it all together\h with the NO_ERRORS_SCHEMA. For additional details\h\h
作为不得已的手段，你可以使用 NO_ERRORS_SCHEMA 来忽略所有此类错误
and examples check out the property binding\h guide in the official Angular documentation.
欲知详情和范例，请参阅 Angular 官方文档的属性绑定指南